{
    "subject": "Maurice_Cloche",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Peppino_e_Violetta",
    "human_readable": "Maurice Cloche directed the film Peppino e Violetta.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9535596370697021,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Maurice Cloche besides Peppino e Violetta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.945846676826477,
            "question": "Who directed the film Peppino e Violetta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9452558755874634,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Maurice Cloche."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8793429136276245,
            "question": "Is Maurice Cloche known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8756146430969238,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Maurice Cloche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6917368769645691,
            "question": "What makes Maurice Cloche a notable director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6165636777877808,
            "question": "What genre is the film Peppino e Violetta likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5661822557449341,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the story of Peppino e Violetta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5168602466583252,
            "question": "What year was Peppino e Violetta released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4329068660736084,
            "question": "What type of work did Maurice Cloche create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maurice Cloche directed the film Peppino e Violetta.",
            "html": "yago_14631_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Peppino e Violetta released?",
            "html": "yago_14631_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the story of Peppino e Violetta?",
            "html": "yago_14631_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Peppino e Violetta likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_14631_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14631_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about various films and their directors. Specifically, document #6 mentions that \"Never Take No for an Answer (also known as Peppino e Violetta and The Small Miracle) is a 1950 Italian film directed by Maurice Cloche\". This confirms that Maurice Cloche directed the film Peppino e Violetta.\n\nSo, according to the context information provided, the triple statement \"Maurice Cloche directed the film Peppino e Violetta\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Maurice Cloche directed the film Peppino e Violetta.\" Specifically, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14631/re-ranker-msmarco/96.txt states that \"Peppino e Violetta (1950) was a Film directed by Maurice Cloche,\" and the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14631/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt mentions \"Never Take No for an Answer (also known as Peppino e Violetta and The Small Miracle) is a 1950 Italian film directed by Maurice Cloche.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}